Jhaal
This kind of slaughter is only done at home.
So I am very happy to be doing everyone's work now.
This is not the action in today's session, but
Now the continuation episode is ready.
Friends, next 2 months
The coming ju mat is very much for all of us
Important: We all consider ourselves grand.
There are many things to do and many things to learn
Friends, this is written by all of you who
Strong Diya Ranjan Sahu is written on the chat
Development Studies by Nishant Joshi Arvind Sir
Jitendra Singh Arya and Harpal Singh Cut
Morning everyone to go episode to start from today
Today is the first Sunday, so this episode
To begin with, this is the purpose of our meeting today.
This is that the quality and growing
Friends, all of you invest in industries.
If you get updates about what you are doing, consider it wrong.
Don't take it for granted or think that what you see today
We will discuss this is the result of ninth.
This is definitely important, but first
Already to please
I have done a lot of research so I have come across a number of things.
He did his job growing latest
Because growing to make money
You will have to invest in interest and Guru
Quality company in the industry
It is important if I invest only positively.
I will do it but it will not work, this yoga should happen every day
I want it, then I will work in it, you will also work.
If there is no need for reading quality then there should be quality too.
If you want, what today's President is doing
He did both these things which back arm
Hey guys, when I initially invested
I am Yash Patel, one of the people who has this problem.
I belong to a chemical like job
I used to invest along with my job, so I
I didn't know that morning interest message
Invested in Blue Chip Suite Breaking
I used to say that I don't know the strategy.
Pocket, this one hour today is very much
It is important that they are already growing
District
Today we did Quality Company Haze and their
Today is the ninth result of quality companies.
This treasure will do the recipe that has been done
Let him tell you that the upcoming enrollee
The results will start from Monday.
We have told you that gas victims will feel that way.
We will go now friend one that Arthur hopes
Do or take action, what are the things you are worried about?
I want to share this presentation with you all.
Make these to-do lists
Before that, tell me that next Sunday also
Stay tuned for Prime Time 90 next week.
You have until Sunday
is the biggest company of quality and we
How many years has everyone been investing?
HDFC Bank is the largest banking
ICICI Lombard General's largest
Result metrics for all three companies are forthcoming.
There is G Raghav Hill which belongs to Rajkot.
Who chop themselves in Bank of Baroda
Do it, he and his team will tell you together
How will the results of the day be and the next
Whatever company's work between Sunday and
The results will come one by one and throughout Sunday.
We are going to discuss the results of these companies.
How to come and what action to take so ready height
Friends, this is for the wealth creation road.
In the ninth, next month we had five
Step-by-Step Wealth Creation Program
Patient for North Indian has been kept
Investors North India Investor Ready
Ho Jae and North India This
From today onwards, my request is that you people should also come to North
Kuntak is very good in Indian language.
in the language in a way that he can understand
So this is our complete mode.
Those who are passing tension are now inviting me.
I have got a chance to show you both the films Singh
right let me invite for staff and
Great Pleasure To Invite In This Village
Magical Chop Tamil in the Mid Day Meal in
If you are working then that of a medical consultant
Beach Boys WhatsApp from Multinational Company
But a drop since last in life years
Due to his reading habits, years ago
Investigate and be active in the stock market
Swings Last One and Half Decade
Hello viewers, catch a flight, Pim Verbeek
Travel Doctor The End of the Lost You Too
Continuous learning has gone into training
In Various Parts of India Workshop
Market January 2018 Hit Training and
Investigators Profit From Living In
Delhi Discover Pehla Mulakat 2018 Hua C
Victim's Family Member of Profit Team and
Look, today Milan Bhai will show it to you all.
I am very happy with this office in China.
Traveling and our visitors are almost varied.
Parts of the country due to its
Contribution to Witnesses and People
Died in objective hospital them everyday
His day routine starts by 4 am.
I am studying and I am active in my job.
Look, still a great investment.
in the sunlight
That request Doctor Mintu unmute
Principal, you all tell me what you get.
A very nice intoxicating point, I will tell you later.
back in Everything Everything Is Awesome and
Students who worked hard in the last quarter
is the last one we've been to so far
There was a lot of meat in it, which made it quite
All the student portals are shining brightly.
It feels great that it's time to do it
Because setting the time to the maximum
It means I have to do at least two things the whole day.
The members also got the company people to do it.
There is a little bit
Yes, but I don't support all of you.
I would like to specially say to Tarun ji Ashok Bhai
Under Vijay Choudhary ji Prashant Khare ji you
It helped a lot with the presentation.
So the profit goes to each team member.
The Shoaib family makes a tremendous contribution.
If we had worked after doing this, then no one would have suffered.
are not occurring
That the track was able to support you
to state Kishan G B is this this
Plate also welcome Jai Kishan ji and we are from Dubai.
Graha is Post Graduate Diploma in
Forest Management and Justified
International Credit Professional Based in
Mumbai from last bank double kia Delhi
by Three Decades Have a Keen Interest
In Stock Market Research and Watching
Cricket Football Let's judge today whether this
The atmosphere of the stock market is like cricket and football.
I love you, say the time at the last second
Only you can tell which one looks like
There is not just one, now it is requested to get it.
Dr. Ajay Mishra Jai ​​Kishan Ji Request
18-year-old teenager
that Rajasthan Sir and waste oil and angry
to thank you thank you to have and have got
Talent Scooby Doo and Professional Life and
This thing has 501 likes in the morning and some time
Specific correct 100 now thanks to both
You took the time to research what we
What to expect from these 2021 results?
I would request both of you to
You guys should see the presentation and I
I would request people to visit the UK
Loot that they my first on the ribbon presentation
Will you forget about your presentation?
Dargah saath ring it once no don't know
Doubt every point and presentation
Ends Enrich Your Point and Theirs
I will try my best to ensure that your fast is
We all have a goal to achieve our value
Creation Ray Channel Thank you very much and
what do you mean by mayank this thank you sir
Friends, I document how profit from
It's Pune, I welcome you all.
As you will see, wealth creation
Quarter ladies and gents in the via
The sequence is that please sir because of ten
Modicare Future has been running us for years
Guides are different quarters
Quarterly results come in reports
so what should we do then I
Friends, I have seen that in the stock market
The revenue minister is getting a bigger day
As best I could tell you, since the last fifteen years
in Maihar to market
That you gave me a lot of trouble in my beginnings.
It happened because some people were their administrators
such a high quality company nearby ok that
But his growth was almost not growth.
But she was different in that and had good returns.
It was available to them but at the price of creation
Nothing happened, so initially the blue chip
I also got involved in this and only Blue
If the color remains, it will be with me in this bundle.
I had a lot of experience and then some time
I was also a growth investor whose
The protest is the fastest, he just invested money
Akshay but that quality was not there i.e.
There was a hydrate button. Margins were quite low.
So as soon as the market falls, the first shock
I used to read tremendously, so I need value eyebrows.
The combination is both together comb
If you do it, it can become profitable.
I have learned from everyone, basically the market
what's going on is that there's just a lot of investment
And there are some people who lean on that person
So let us not go into growth and value
If we walk together hand in hand
profit of
It is formed and great in the West long term
As we will see,
Quarterly results as of today
If someone finds it useful in the description
Friends, today's question is all about
Anniversary will work as per today
What is the circuit of discussion and why did we keep it
It was as difficult today as you reported.
Will keep watching and as soon as part 1 part 2 and
quarter okay we keep the results we
given by labels and at that level a lot of
I got a call from the mission, why are you crying so much?
Welcome to the good level that for the minute
And a lot of queries also came regarding that.
Admin on behalf of Profit From It
What to Report Animal Results For
If so, give this good news to all of them.
I want you to have a lot of fun in the next two months.
A great opportunity is about to come
If you see the presentation, the quarter
What is the result of the quarter four?
Expect Quarter Fore Result
Friends, we have to see that our
Which stop should we put in the portfolio?
Reduce any system weights which stop
Increase the weightage and where will the waste come from?
Because as I said, the value and
Both groups are important, so we group
Friends, we will type and make profit.
I'll track in change with him high
Quality company if ever there will be a combination
If it will be a great loss then it will be in the neck line friends
We will see that all of us who start in Valid
The warden then lived his best
Court Has Price War on Tube End Values
that you get so like what we do like
We go to buy vegetables, you call it the market
I feel the same way every time I stay in the past
If you look at the experience of even one year,
Last 4 Nifty direct from 12,000
It had fallen to 8000 and that time we image
These were not made of such high quality
Stocks that you think are solutions, these stocks are my
You should stay in a bundle so big that you
It was related but now the atmosphere is so scary
I had gone and no one would have education.
It's very difficult to make that decision.
To them and then I ji have said the same thing that
Shock or stock you should definitely watch
I get it for less money
How to get good quality at low cost
Good quality only and only market
Friends, even today if we look
So the commenting environment is going on very loudly.
And in this environment you would smoke a cigarette
so we're not exactly one and a half like it
taught us that if there is any market call
You should have a list of Agro
industries and it is the best in it
If there is a company then high quality merchandise is available.
And inside Fit has written Bike is like
Buying high quality merchandise
If you put tomatoes then when is this accident going to happen?
It is possible that long gowns may be worn from tomorrow or the day after.
And quite good in the subject market too
If there is a correction, we will have your list play ready.
If you have brought it then you must have it
Take advantage and tell me in one thing
I would like friends who initially also wanted me to
We had a lot of trouble with the tractor.
It is important that initially I
He talks behind his back, this company is good, he
Told that the company is good, it is a blue chip
If you are very good at it, then you don't earn any money from it.
My friends who became my 10 year old
from another but if you focus on the sector
You do it because it is always about group chapters.
If the stock comes after the sector, then the
There is the best demand in the sector
More profit is being made, for example, you
If you look at the retail industry right now,
You will see that Reliance Capital is wiping out
If demand is coming then it is in the retail sector.
This is a great moment, 40 years ago
This was the situation with Walmart's partner.
Walmart's beginnings in the US
That system came a year ago and today it is a
The sector has matured and Walmart has
If you make people 100 times more money, then give it to them.
The sector is therefore important if we
We will see that the retail sector is doing well.
So the good company in the sector in the list
I should see it, so friends and
Why should we invest?
In growing sectors, the answer is this
It is in front of you, see what peace has become of the people.
It happens that common people always go to the post office
National Savings Certificate Monthly Income Scheme
and retired senior citizens thing that
That in different government schemes
Investing according to security
If yes, then what is the interest rate?
Friends, four percent, five percent, and
Half percent to senior citizens but
The rate of inflation is 50 percent.
And that's on paper, friends, because real
If you look at the rates of things in life
What is there keeps increasing a lot.
Children's education and our retirement too
If we have to make provisions for it then
So we need to beat inflation at double the speed.
If you have to do it then the biggest question that comes up is
How do I set inflation for friends?
How do I make a good investment?
The answer is the fastest growing industry, us.
From August to seven percent, I will also cry.
We are getting a litre and from that we get fifteen thousand rupees.
20 cents on the cent hungry-led
The best industry we could find
The thing will remain friends because if our
from seven percent after accounting for inflation
If you go ahead, this will become a great will.
I would like to tell you one thing, Warren Buffett.
when we sat down
A little fears so cry aa to twenty percent
The return of Anjali is unmistakable but
He is the world's richest investor, so if
We are very lucky that India's Fastest
Growing economy is one of the largest economies in the world.
With the fastest growing economy
Fastest Growing Industries are also money
Which are the fastest growing industries?
Will set up friends in which we
You should invest so that yours becomes legitimate.
Also, your pitcher plant will help your children grow healthy.
For family or retirement goals
If we do it, which centres will be there in it?
If we make good investments then it
One should visit Sector-7 and see the system
After we find out that in the sector
There is a lot of demand so we need that chapter.
Which is the best company that has a meter
process which is like this in the classroom
If you teach then which company sells best
Make the best profit you can
At least we are doing the minimum whose quality
The net profit margin is the best
Stay because friends, if any company
She does business and there is no sale.
So there is no question of profit.
You fear years after all expressions if
If margins are not good then companies
Next good trick not taking profits at home
If it can go then whatever is growing in India
Sectors that are making a lot of money
If so, let me tell you some examples.
I would definitely like to do advertising and
Media is the sector of the officer in which Apple
If the company is there, then as the future taught us
As I remember, a year and a half ago, two years ago
First Step in Delhi at the first campus
If action was taken then it would be for India.
There was a discussion about this and it is a new sector
And let's go to Kurukshetra, hmm, I also guided you.
and you grew four or five times from there
So friends, the salt center has a different
He lives in the same four, his growth rate is heavy
lives and if you look at healthcare
Industry like the red path is still in the past
If you look at the record of the week, the red path will be
Lab has made a lot of money
Due to withdrawal in Dene Pharmaceuticals
All the situations are good
I have seen many groups of famous actors.
What was the condition of the pharma sector a year and a half ago?
It's cooled down and IT consulting
Software's Serious and the rest of this company
If it is making waves then this is the most
The important thing is some tractors we
We will see and look into the details, friends.
Another problem with people is if they
If you don't listen to a high quality company, it's like
The volume is then stated by G that these
This economic mode of business is considered as
What is the meaning of vote in simple language?
I will speak in the language of the common layman
High quality company which company is
Do good business in good situation
Make good profits with minimal expenditure
Work at least he has a loan and
If he has the best management
This is what Warren Buffett calls mood.
High quality company speaks quality
The company's friends have the most advantage
There is a big advantage when the market is fruitful.
If it happens then these quality companies are very few.
You will see that it gives to meat
In time also some companies have launched new life in
had imposed
So friends put it that his mood was quite
It was good that his investment was the best.
It is important that these quality companies
One should keep in mind that many
The investor will keep in mind that all these things
ok what have you brought for us
Jai Kishan ji and I and the whole
The Profit team has created some great
It is a growing sector and has been found and brought to you.
and that which is from the growing sector, if
If you see, it is a good top most company.
What a group, standing on this and in the whole
What is obscene, so friends, these 50 companies
How does it fit into your portfolio?
How much quantity should be kept?
If we want a detailed presentation of this, we will do it.
If you are going to do so, I request all of you.
I will tell you that this presentation is for you.
Listen carefully to what we will tell you.
You can adjust your portfolio accordingly.
And every Sunday you get a new
Multibagger details and reset annually
Once the reports are discussed by the officer, I
I welcome Jai Kishan ji and both of us.
Together you get Rs. from 50 companies
will start and what action to take in it
He will tell you a
That they will find unfit your wonderful late
Aaungi platform and its types of the
Guy's Actors and Growing Company is OK
First Advertising & Media It's One of
The Most Amazing Sectors in India
I am Hans Vinod till print media this time
and Digital Media Stitching Mock Test
Media this growing 80 per cent cut out of
witch mobile site
Scoring item a little speed post
Options such company in India which has * and
mobile platform so we can set up here
There was hardly any impact of action scenes.
During your time and factories growth and
What are they expecting this horoscope?
Dhrol 50% European Rebellion Solve Growing
fs14 long term basis will expect this
Company to Attack Conservative Reed Unification
Win at least 80% off your favorites
Saint of the next decade friends who is
That's very interesting Internet software
and services whenever you have done any railway
The booking will be done by the bank in its own bank.
If you keep the money deposited, you will remain bowed down.
Cloud computing when you receive an SMS
Internet comes into service
The company which provides rot mobile in loot service
He is a great high quality company, Hero.
company if we look at it in the section
The best growth that you have achieved is your
If we have done it then Animalia will see that 40%
We expect sales and
The rapid growth of profits is due to
This is not a major expense for the company.
All this with minimum manpower and no problem for them.
If the material is not available then its profit
We have a lot of people standing 100% on this.
Till we can see profit this quarter
and its great in the long term
If it is there then it is absolutely a quality company.
Please do like the post, thank you Milni
Need a Sector Life Insurance Term
Life insurance sector is under control
Posted by LIC policy is 66 now currently
LIC is not a listed company
In Respective Status Teacup Life Which
Has Marked 051 14%
Written Screwing Initials Dewar Slide One
Cup-Winning Lead Over Time But They Have Recovered
Wonderfully Well and Expecting Director
Pay aa sexual past 3333 on cent growth to
The Profitability Will Review Flags
Insurance Sector Life Insurance Sector
Expected to grow at almost 3 per cent
End Expectant CSC Live ₹2
Fielding 20% ​​if you
He has come, thank you Jai Kishan ji, yes friends.
The sector is that of agro chemicals.
Agrochemicals means agriculture company
Companies that work in agriculture
And if it provides chemicals then drink it in it.
The industry is a strong company with small
It is a company but it is a high quality company.
In which we will see that twenty per cent
Growth we really expect and
Growth is a shift percentage, so the most
The important thing is friends that even today we
India's economy is still a developing nation
A lot depends on agriculture and
We will see that agriculture like login
It will grow and the rest of the things will happen and then
If medicine becomes like this then people will come back
If there is a motor towards agriculture then it is B
Demand can be seen in this sector.
So I would like to tell you that five-six years ago
Future made a love interaction video
where he is 5065 rate na sir its 10 12 years
first or of the industry and that Azhar 12 all
If I'm going forward, these magical things
It happens if you
If the problem stays with the company, your
A tremendous will is made
The next sector where terrorists will be found is housing.
HPSC is going to introduce this in Finance Housing Finance
Lead Up
Who is chief executive officer of HDFC?
Bank HDFC Life is Payer Go Plus Inka
own
death due to this decision they etc latest
Expecting That Defines President
Profitability Notification Airport End
Appeared in the negative 14.5 and is looking more
Industrial dishonest free sent on this channel
Of the GDP demote dish on thick stand
Cent of the GDP well s in China get a
St. and Western on Strong meeting
World It's Madden Fifty Percent to 0.2
In the distance to pause anger so long term
Expecting this Sector-20 again and
Almost Kunwar San Target
Are you there or those, thank you Jai Kishan ji, yes friends
The next set of services is telecom services.
This is a turnaround sector, friends.
After Joe's entry, a lot of this chapter
The rest of the players and a lot of them
losses were incurred and a lot of revenue and
Business Judge and this is what we cover in digital
But in this too Bharti Airtel itself
Maintained and positioned itself very well
If you are strong in this way, then this chapter
It was running in the Continuous Last, right now
Coming in last profit we will see that
This year the revenue is twenty five percent
This is our Android group.
Friends, this is the drone on the front.
If the last profit is there then I will run the company properly.
High quality will have to be tracked in this
If you get any red gown, please take it.
You have to do it for one minute at low level.
Rising Unit Situation but not us ourselves
I have to study because this centre is quite
This bull will show quality and last profit.
When the company comes, that constable is there
It takes time and the consistency is less in it.
There remains an end to profit
One, whenever an edit is found, 1 at the lower level
Minutes and as many profits end this
Jersey consistency is definitely clear to us.
You should get the mixture after this
Edison Famous Key Cheese Activate of Consumer
Products Devi Central Khane Mode of
Tata Chemicals Organization Global Service to Form
Tata Consumer Products Presents Team
Management 2007blsim has sacrificed at which
Expect this high growing sector in
India Now Residency Deol City Delivery
Mushroom production is also done by this and this company
Expecting to provide 30 cents receiver
With profits from 27th Sept no water
Management has done its best for tough toe consumers.
Products Set The Fabricated And Focused
Upon doing this company Audi A3 lights
GDP
Tu Polytechnic Craft [ __ ] 500 and
Actress Supriya Aaron bought only six bikes
& Companies from near Noida Sector 29
If realization happens then private banks
Entry was made and the entire private bank
Focusing on developing his fans was his
not the focus but in the last few years we
You will see that brinjal is grown in very rural areas.
I focused on them at the very least and
It is what it is, but we'll see that in fact
What happened because of this, if it happened then it is enough
Sare Small Finance Bank Quality Company
and that of which he
A rural economic collapse has caused us to
If you see, the profit is down, then we have to pay a little
We will have to stop there to be English.
We don't need domination at the lower level
Do it and keep in mind that Bigg Boss
Like what is inspector issue profit
If we had opposed it from the end then we would have
It has been at a lower level since August.
should be activated gradually
to knife my song next next a like
I will meet you, I told you earlier
Pharmaceuticals a Boeing Sector from Behind
And the best quality company in this sector
China Does Not Lose Its Fight for Quality
Voice is on best company which class ix
Crying and Expecting a Thing
British 20% Profits Growing Guest
Post Office Prince Office Company is that was
Caught with high quality compliance
and Ping Plastics Relationship with Pharma
Companies World Wide Protests by
BJP leaders in AP INV expect
Complete this chapter to grow and become wiser.
Grow On Trees and tagged Solid One Company
That you want to pharmaceutical companies that
You Need to Have Devils in Your Portfolio
State coordinator Krishna ji is from Sector 20.
of personal products which have been around for a long time
And I will speak in every sector because you
Everyday things that seem personal
Hindustan comes in products
From Unilever's Live Boy to many others
If you use brand then it will be mentioned in this chapter
There was a lot of excitement among people because of the long gown.
Hindustan Unilever has seen good growth
Acquisition of Blackshirt SmithKline
If done then they have to do inorganic growth.
If we have benefited, we will see that throughout this year
We expect 28 percent growth in
Can make these profits in thirty per cent but
This growth is organic, it must be kept in mind
electronic by keeping it in
Hindustan Unilever benefits because of this
which has brought back the growth rate in the future term.
It won't last that long and may come down.
We have this quality company, good Twitter.
But she does it thinking that the group will remain moderate.
We should click on Lower Level as well.
Healthcare services will be available, Sendha Growing
Sector in India and its role in
Best company is Agyan Hips Dr Lal Path
Lab which has the largest notification other
This is for independent escorts in India
Presents Quiet had slide tempera
But you can see how they 28 required and this
Expecting more than 70% growth between
And profitability of chronic 10 per cent
Again in this sector also be displayed in
Lower inflation and higher costs for growth and
Dr Lal Path Lab Ping Reader Pro
Quantity also taking advantage of 80
Producer Company and Fight for Co Mute
During an option correction, friends complete
IT Consulting & Software in the world
The companies are running at a tremendous pace
You will remember how Infosys started
I made good money first and gave it to you
I would like to add one more thing to Larson and
Toubro was the original construction company
But as we look, we have to
If that construction
The company lived Larsen & Toubro Infotech
They reside in them but these companies
When we grow up, we should learn this.
Whatever happens to the company, that too should remain.
Larson in IT Consulting and Software
& Toubro is a very big company, one of its
Very good, we will see
That sister Santa Long at the top of the profit
Its very around 15 to 20 in term
It will be of cents and it will be good for calibration.
There is a possibility whenever there is a
You must like deposit correction, thank you.
You will find products now in IT Shop.
Leading companies in this sector are Tata Elxsi
Ltd. 6981 C This Sintu Artificial
Intelligence Big Data Charts Used to Exist
The train was late by half an hour.
Reality Internet of Things Diseases Fix
whereby this used using statement end
Expect Tak Paytm ft Step Off This
The segment is also comfortable 3311
that film mitti shueib mamachand setting stop
What a great potential threat and all
This technology is an issue watching and this app
craft style etc. Right Support for Frying
Accessible to PAN
A Lookout for the Best Companies in the System
And artificial pin the best tried toe
Uplift Tips
Even today I commented expecting an egg follow
Set Thirty Per St. Vincent 6% With
profits persons this use potential and
Effective You Can Expect Exponential
Growth fennel make on this effective end
Specially Tata Elxsi next friends who
center is that plastic products so that
Investors keep in mind that plastic
But there is a ban on plastic, well I tell you this
I would like to tell that those who are in agriculture
Do we take it or whatever we feel in the society?
are used to do their whole those
All should be replaced with plastic pipes
has been and plastic pack abs work
It is good and much more than life change
This remains the most important chapter we
We will see
So plastic is the supreme industry in that
Best company under this, cents on these
Expecting growth and profit
They also have 75% births in
And he also has plans to launch a channel soon, so that
The development that is going on in rural areas also
Construction is going on in full swing
So plastic pipes are being used everywhere.
If you have plastic products, you need them a lot.
Good growing sector is this recipe dip
I must take it that we will meet a
Sector is five ask updater rule this piece
In between, their market share of
Thirty percent and this company has been given
Connect with Fears and Tips You
And me Tilak's meeting press this
Company World War Two being our out.
Turning point: You can see this suit abroad.
In activity of this company oo
I call them pornographic during format
The Sikander option is net a specific growth
Have That Clay Lock Dance Coming in Egypt
Fall in office school fat condoms improve them
Impacted Testicles and Examine Them
only profitability spider-man ficci
Confidence Palm Oil Tight Price Hai Who You
Pure management as doing is there anything
deficit and have that cost-efficient thing
Love and kind management seniors
Tubelight protest apology from market increase
6 unmute cost efficient sis 63 right toe
Grow and expecting a this company to serve
hair growth
That this is thank you Jai Kishan ji, yes friends
The sector is very interesting, check it out.
Golden Companies Holding Company is a
Production does not continue, it goes to other companies
shares of melt cycles and those who
Holding companies make profits there.
If we get it then we will see in this Bajaj
There is a company like Finserv in which Bajaj
Bajaj also wants shares in finance
Allianz also has insurance business
If it is there then its dross is natural for them.
I do not incur any expenses. I do not spend any money.
If the deposit remains in this holding company then their
protest that we will see on frill send
Expect us in sales and from Joe
This misinterprets their visual company as their
Also prevents these trophy 2017 is cent but
As I say, by making any investment
Holding companies do their own right
I don't need him to go if his
If it is your own quality study then definitely
He purchases his own tours.
He has to have a different right over the holding company
Not required
So you will get only one like Nagdev picture
Company Nestle from different food industry
The excerpt is leaked that chord on 95 cent market
Share in these food and five per cent in Udan
OK Khasi Indian Economic Growth Consumption
Milk from unknown uie taboo laughing
Potential Toubro Mouni Behind Diffusion Free
Difficult Expectations of a Sonth Person
Much of iodine currently e hv expecting
Dead Cells Relationship Rock P Expecting
Recovery and value is the road, so more than that
Increase Profitability Twist It
Impact will endeavour of True Saints Pat
Inky Shifts Quality Company
that they have connection ODF vacuum crate
yes
A play by Kishanji Ignorance Friends Person
The excise tax sector is starting well.
So in which we had written Hindustan
Unilever is that multinational company and we
Will see India's notification company Godrej
Consumer Shetty, who is not in your country
Nepal Bangladesh is our neighboring country and
Exports to many countries
Like you did and its shop will remain there.
If you use mosquito repellent, as soon as
With Hindustan Unilever, we
If you contact Hindustan Unilever
It is a very old company and has a problem
The decision has been made, but it is quite
Companies like Gurjar Recipe are currently
It is in a primitive stage, it is better than here
There is a group, so we will see that
12 percent growth expected in the process
Twenty-five percent of the end profit
So, I am talking about Indian multinationals.
Any deposit should definitely be focused on
There is a correction, we can definitely try it.
I will get the next area marked
Biotechnology expert working
Set up which has left potential end
Biocon is leader in destructive
Definitely Biocon, this look initially
Devoted Quiet Vik Patel Vinay Slide Tap
And expecting a devil and you with no
Point in the growth and rise
Profitability vote for thumb down 12531
First, but this might be no opportunity
Tipp Point Correction Districts Take Off
Unity 282 Travels in Respective
Biocon SHO Possible as Another Amar Singh
Sectors which should be coming off the food chain and
Mix and admin full chapter dry result
Payo full yes thank you friends ne sector
by difference
As we will see, every year our
The budget for defense is a budget of difference.
It keeps growing because our
The neighbor is Pakistan and channels like
There are countries with which we always have relations
If only India is suffering then
Electronics is the best company among them
that makes products for difference if
We are a great peace company, friends, so this
Definitely, there is a lot of growth effect in this.
No, send it to bed, we are watching.
Usually sent in profits from the middle end
Do it and see, I will tell you that
There is absolutely no need to address immediately.
There is no need to look for long term growth
There's a rough growth for us like the dip we get
should like bird immediately if so
We don't need to take any action
Is
So PAN will get additional territory
Electrical Equipments and Syster Ac
Paste Thandi Quality Company Aircel India
Initially during liquid democracy on this
Plastic Impacted Pathan Still of Tom
Talking about frequency values ​​from
Recovery for the Products and Ware
Expecting Into Flowers Patient Growth
and 3714 Sure Profit Senior Navodaya
Sector is expected to grow by 305
Semester Subject Company Definitely Morning
Outperforming and Pending Industries
Shifted Toe Reduces a Lookout for Kids
Even Kishanji's friends have
This is a chapter of general insurance.
It is an emerging sector and if you are a developing
If you do less than Nation, General Issaka
The sector is quite big and the things there
This is a company like China's pin company.
There are many large companies that
If we look at the comparison, in India
It has just begun, so the banks are closed from here.
The journey of circulation begins
This chapter contains such lines but the best
Making profits and getting the best high
It is a quality company as you will see.
The economic condition of the people throughout the year
If the network was bad then definitely insurance
The sector has been hit hard, so we
Seeing that there were quite a few lost but he
Five percent profit we earn annually
Expect Sales in Rajouri Sector
These profits have been the growth factor of fashion.
The 23-year-old's butt in this chapter
It is an emerging sector, we are confident about it.
We have to keep in mind that whatever record we make, we will improve it.
if it happens then
You will see up multibagger in that system.
So if you don't do such ok bye but people
Please comment on that
So PAN will get the next SIT
Consulting and software in this sector leg
Till TCS is closer to lead an Indian
Leaders But One of the Global Leaders Also
When IT services with revenue for
Twenty-Two Billion Dollars and the Architect
OF 150 Belgium Spain A Consistent
Compound of paw mini years this year will be
Slide Impact and Without Expecting
Much Truth Will Be Destroyed All Saints End
Prophet's Food also all most of life but
System Mufti Industries and Loop Looking
and technology to help them find the truth
TCS is appallingly song
That attempted spot will be off dega bean
Used a turn of running staff in the morning
Person looking out for PC in this
Sector and quite often depicted in
These porn dudes who are in private
Banks like New Admission Hua and Private
When the bank entry was made, he said that
All the focus is on industrial players.
It was started and India was a developing nation.
Therefore, this private bank is doing very well.
There is a big question in everyone's mind.
If you have already grown up and you are older, I will tell you
I would like to tell you that tea and this is here
It's been 10 minutes since I've watched it comfortably, so I
Definitely you should say different.
Investment should be made
So definitely add termination to this year.
Vida in fact that moral moratorium chief x6
And four years as opposed to 4% we're currently at this X
Factor in sales and profits
are protesting against 14% but now I
I would definitely like you to find someone ideal
Shares that are more than 100% reliable
If yes, then you must focus on HDFC Bank.
do
A drama Milegi Next a fan specific GN
B.Sc. Non-Banking Financial Companies in
Registered Pest Company Fit Proft Is Bajaj
Finance 955 Str's Husband Co Enough Power
Saint
That Awadhi this is only YouTube's middle name
Text Specific Company Was Trying To
Conserve Tell Radha Bank Dargan Lakh every morning
Expecting Days Only for Person Growth
and profitability it but also benefited
Through the Snow Dahan Expecting a Baby
Boy Dance Falls But Don't Thing Since The
Company Hus Declared Spoon Number Adult
Suggesting Missile King Talk Request This
Decision Start Appeal Equity Plants Pink
Year started 2506 March Three Four States Has
Come Down To Sixteen Thousand Words Witch
Mean Specific Company Sparing Tank
Positive and Success Looking to Deposit Money of
Truth Should Look Out For This Company Unfit
Listening Tips Praty To Complete Singh Ke
Music Friends Sector Bank Hai Bank Mein
We've been watching Last for many years and
The protests were also not good but in the last one or two
If we look at the year, their MPs are growing rapidly.
were decreasing and were found in many groups
and the best bank in it
State Bank of India is about
I would like to tell you some interesting facts like
that the population of USA is between 3.5 billion
I am in and State Bank of India
The account holder has an account of Rs. 1 crore.
There is a big difference between State Bank of India and
of India as soon as Amar Singh Sector
If you do this then SBI Card will be used for SBI Life.
Insurance SBI ATM C Inki Jo
We get subsidies up to 15-20 percent.
If Agro is visible then the benefit of all this is State
Bank of India This is going to happen to that group
If yes, then this is a good sector in the long term.
will remain defeated
Then the MP front camera to render in
If there were facts, we would not be aggressive at all.
We should be activated at the lower level
We should set our expectations for the whole year
It will be favorable if you look at it, we will focus on it at 4%
They are doing this and making profits in it.
Temple Run may happen but between the two you
Activate forward at lower level
Not made at all
So you will find only one, the next sector is
Cement Ka End Ultratrac Easi Largest
cement company in india
So initially, due to VAT, they also
It snowed but since 16th construction
Activity Destroyed Government
Spending Wins from Date of Birth
Expecting a to zip code and cent growth
in the country point in hindi profits
For future like India Skin and
Fabricated Market Jyoti Lab Zo World
Average is sentence mission formed speak
Profit is from CO2 cheese and extend
200 250 Asyum Science Specific
Artist to Group Result A Pinch Ali
Difficult Want a Joint Secretary Sanjay
20 Sector Furniture Paint Paint Company
If we talk about this, there is Asian Paints which we
Ginger and multibagger can speak because
pitch
Since this year, the consistency with which
By making it non-profit, there is no solution to it.
No, it is all over the world and actually its
We will say logistics company because 40
A year ago, he started data collection and
How is the distributor network?
If it is produced according to
This chapter is very good growing different
I loved matures like you'll see quarters.
I was in a loss in one, I opened a lot of buttons and lost
Free percent ahead in loss of profit
an important source of
In this, 60% of these profits are very high.
Quality company is a minute definitely karni
As soon as the market falls a little bit
As it is, an atmosphere of fear is being created right now.
One should take advantage of the Dargah
I am Ankit Milegi Vriksha Actor is Iron
And steal again in this sector paste thandi
Quality Company SJW Skill
Vinayak was born in the initial over time
Sales Maximum Length Photo Only One Person But
Again Due to Government Spending and Fall
of wickets required and stolen
Demand It's Coming Back and Expecting
That the feel that I would use to ignore
Scent and Profitability at Shilpi Desi
Award Group F-35 Question Advance Dash Love
and W.H. Hussain wicket 30
Doctor Hindi Porn Stars Shop and Win
World Cup cut consumption of ministerial is
Start with 229 cups of sugar.
Hai Waise In India South Mixture ₹70
Venue One Use Rohini Sector 5 V Can
Expect slow penetration
Even what Kishore ji's friends have said
The joints sector is India's largest
It is one of the fastest growing sectors
Department stores and departments
Avengers and Super Mario Bros. in stores
Kishan is a German company, so among friends
I want to tell you that for this
Like 40 years ago in our corners today
The condition in which she was from the US and she
started like Walmart and people
If it gives multibagger returns then it can be done in India too
Friends, from the beginning, Avni Super Mart
We have a variety of issues on the smaller side of the model.
From here you can see that the biggest one is
The player is Reliance Retail and also a twist
If it hasn't happened then we need treatment.
The video is Super Matka featuring Radha Kishan
Like these mean refusal from the promoter long
The track record is very good
With management, I definitely have any
People should keep an eye on supermarkets.
Because we will see a lot of sales
I was down, that's why I lost
per
He recovered in the way thing in the quarters
and it will come to plus one percent that when
Very Good The Adverse Se Profit Man 20% Less
If you look at the dip, this is the impression that comes
So definitely we should do it for a minute.
Main Ankit Milenge Mixture is Hair End
This TTK Prestige Agreem The Best Hot
Company Initial Tweet Timing 5 Years
Sees Bataunga Effective Work House From
Leader has recovered one speak now he started
Talking of and expecting scene one
Platform Sales and Profitability Have
A good thing is more team management of this
The company would like to group organic farming and
In organic tea and management is
Casting come want to feel see turn over
Internet Story Yes Interruption Pulse Company End
Network Liquid Dips also discussed a lot
I have auto parts and equipments like
Electric vehicles are in the running, so
So the focus of their vehicles is decreasing.
In this chapter, this video is from many channels.
type is that straight into unfolding
There is a lot of uncertainty, this ignorance is auto
Parts and Equipment with Economy
The economy can only run if it remains from
Definitely, it shows economic growth.
If it happens then this chapter is also slow
Complete the next economic year and don't do it.
If there is one, then definitely Spiderman will be in it.
Lower star sales of 37 percent
In that he will mix that while recovering
Came to minus one percent and profit baby
If we come to set to minus one, then the address in this
There is absolutely no need to be gradual
We will see if it can be profitable.
As growth improves, we gradually
If people do 1 minute at the level
So feel free to get the next update on the internet.
Software and services in this sector
This is from leading company Aircel
Inside we have officer enlightenment Alexey
Song in this sector tuition also people naac
Scene
Also known as Expecting a Sweetheart Negro
BP Expecting a Two Close Fix
Negative Two Per Cent Growth and Forty
percent Edison made profits at
E-mail PTS only 11017 and desktop
Customers have already saved around 218
6pm Surya You Can Imagine This Form Rudhir
This company handset part reading engineering
Research and Development Services Company In
India so past turn of unity drink
Correction and Begusarai Two of Units Companies
Choli this thank you friends sector in this
I've made a lot of money recently
Specialty Chemicals Check Two Specialties
Chemicals tractors benefit the most
What is happening is anti-channel sentiments.
Make India self-reliant, self-reliant India
The project is Make in India, so it
Whatever chemicals came from China, they were
Companies have closed down and some companies have
The product is sitting outside and WhatsApp is double
Players also want him to be from China.
Do not purchase goods and
The growing industrialization of things
Because Specialty Chemicals act as a
It is going to give tremendous returns, the best among these
Pidilite is a good company.
Fabric will feel sorry for Wick Wick and
Soil and Doctor used in the last week
If done then the product is because of the long gown
I did not see the shift in the last quarter
Percent Cardiff was when it I recover
In the meantime, we will discuss this - up to 100%
came and lost to problems ninety-five
From percent to now plus six percent
If some companies come into your portfolio
There must be one of the company
Apple Divide like dips got definitely
Activate Aggressive at Lower Levels
There are absolutely no leads like the one you will get
You can get it now, so please like it.
Thank you, you will get a lot of money.
and it needs an irrigation to cool down
Definitely from the fold of Rupinder Company
What can be the correction in a
that their side also has vitamin fast from
Serious Difficulties But You Can See House
From seed company is required and just
Chill expecting dat's it in the negative
cent and profitability of that person
2% Pat Disturb Karenge Click 1600 End
Expect to grow at 22.81 Road Voltas
Pingali Double Definitely's Dhanwan Switch Off
This fruit subscribes to the opium list
Voltas Urine Tears Yes Thank You Jai Kishan Ji
discuss about it as you all
You know, earlier this year we had a
There were slippers which you might remember as flip flops.
and Bruce Lee, but today we will see
Our office has different lives.
and lives separately from Kajol, so all this
So why is development happening, friends?
As India's economy is growing, people
If money is coming near you then spending habits
This is changing, B division is pending.
Keep in mind that look like
Companies are becoming global leaders in court.
In the footwear industry, footwear
Industry has many products and practices
India's economy is growing
Population Global Demand Looked at This Way
If you go, Relaxo Footwear is a great
The multibagger has already started, whose
We will see what our profit will be in a year.
Expressed his tales us - five percent
is expected to office at Central
He was in the hospital for quite some time.
After improvement, this group up to - percent
If we look at the end profit
Thirty-five percent to fifteen percent
When it is invested in profit then at
It will stop from sleeping state if woken up
This is a lot of returns, if you look at us
isn't it, thank you madam ji, next
Construction Engineering and in this
Sector Pleader 1570 E
So initially this is with Tehsil Part Pathan
What is seen as a construction
Activity in India has been picked up and worn
Expecting an attack from Arvind negative
Five Questions Shape Profitability
Vote Provide Thirty Percent HCF
That Popular is a trusted company
Squat Use Proof Potentials and
Currently Yes See The Question Is It Is A
Available at very attractive valuations
Breastfeeding Normally for Husband Forward Peacock
Historic Chittar Artists from this is
Pet Hus Always Comes Back Sophia Looking For
Export Company To-Do List
Today's India Construction Engineering
Sector Look Talent Ki Friends A Special
Bus service has a new one, friends, if we
If we talk about developed nations, what is there
companies, this is how he manages to build his team with companies like
is a hundred times bigger company than
what happens in development is that they
If needed, companies provide
Companies like that have work to do
and it reduces the expenses and
Some don't stay because they have no
They don't have the manpower to produce
The attorney lives only as the team
companies that are visible but it in
Quality is the company, so we definitely focus on it.
should be careful because of people and
Natural staff due to economic slowdown
What happened last year is going to change very soon.
And as you will see, it was bloody still.
profit
I have fifty percent because their expenses
If nothing else, it's a different type of business.
If there is a different type of will industry then
Definitely a lot of money can be made in this.
Regulation at the lower level is a must.
should be done but should go gradually if
There is no need for it to be like this
A drama hymn song
Ink System Specification for Anything
And peanuts and press the top companies workers.
Sister, this is just a mixed leader in India.
Rajasthan More Company Date Free Initial
Liquid Thank You in the Next Process
60% of the value is from quotes 54 - 68
Speak what and expecting a glass of ice
Negative six and a quarter inch wicket
Profitability Growth of Innocent Now In
This sector loot guru is next 9 met
Producer and if you want to take good
Company Front Shramik Sector Is Acharya
Friends, 2323 we are about basic transport.
Because if you are not able to do it then their too
Three wheeler will be the best option if
We
If you look at the best company in India, then Bajaj Auto
which has been there for the last thirty-forty-fifty years
Bajaj Auto's budget hotels are in the works
Indian multinational company
The company has many companies in many countries.
Products Three Wheeler from this system Miller
Two wheelers are sold which range from basic to
If it is up to the advanced model then this but this chapter
It is always volatile because it
Tractor Sicklekar is economical
whose impact we will see that - Seven
But send their head which we click then
60% - in After One so from there -
Seven percent is a good group, it is the last one.
We can say that profits are increasing gradually.
And if we look at the profit from it,
- But cent of profits is printed but
Yes, in this sector there is no possibility of becoming invisible.
There is absolutely no need for lower levels and
Combination definitely for the long term
The next system is a
Management is
that the pest quality of this sector counts
The company HTC Handset Management initially
During World Cycle AIIMS
Database Migration and Craft In
Revenue of 84 cents spot fixing now
It's Last Quarter Tax Sequential
Growth and Were Expecting a
Sequential Guru to Continue Sudhir
Revenue Sports TV Town Phase -
Questions Leaves Acid Citric Update DSC
Ko Mute Buddhi Court Management Thal Der
Expenses and what they can expect
Profit From This Point System
Expecting to get 8th of almost 50%
and shifted in this app you can laugh between
Like mutual love, there is space and width
Friends in which Madrasan Sumi Do
That company is an Indian multinational company
It is prescribed in many countries
There is support, but we will see how this works.
Lots of charges in the sector too
Coming because of electric vehicles
So the role of Madrasan Sumi is that of those small
Making parts for vehicles, which has a lot
Will all the points be applied in the future or
Will not be installed or different types of development
But we will find out and as we will see
Fifty percent was involved which is a natural
Because of the liquid, we are nine percent -
Growth in - You can see these profits in
If I can see 14% then definitely this
There is no point in being aggressive in the chapter.
It definitely is and should remain Android, but
Agents need not take any action in this
Hey thank you, I will meet you next Sector 12 Arts
New Delhi vacancies in this segment
Maruti is its best quality company
Tags Page 9 Tags Page 10 Days 50% Off
So initially point time around fifty
percent of sales were from because of
Lord Sun 28 such remedy opening of waves
Seen a user page setup demand and still
Have Recovered Panchagavya Expecting Next
100 Years - Questions Page Stripping by
12% Patwa Office Infrared * CS Month Month
Month Dev Number Sa Growing and Touch Parthiv
YouTube Entertainment & Events
Production Capacity: 512 Look
And take good company in from distant
Maruti Established A
That this decision was taken by Kishan ji, yes friends.
Texture is that Amar Singh sector is internet
and catalogue retailing, so it is an immortal
Singh Sector and Amar Singh Sector
A lot of money is made, friends, because
It gets trimendous growth if India
If we look at it then by doing insurance
The company whose naukri.com dinner is 99acres
Like the Yagya companies from their list side
There is no production, no service
These people provide it, so you will see
Whether it's a long gown or anything else
There will be complications after growth.
They don't have much impact, only 12% -
Less needed but much bigger in profit
If there is a jump then this is the lotus, friends.
Internet related companies have no
The old man who lived in the expressway was his last
If the year KV line draw remains then those who
If revenue is received then profit is made from it.
It is that the new lines have also reduced due to some reason
They don't mind being kept in a temporary refrigerator.
If it falls then it is a unique product of different quality.
It is a company in this field and
Must have in portfolio
But there must be regulation on that.
If the soup is not ready
That expensive watch is the next one from France
Kaa & Mr Bean The Quality & Best
The company launched Tubelight for drops of
What time will it be for all these sectors to get VAT?
Passed and still has 75 NFC off
Badnaami opening of from - and also 60% in
Expecting a 2012 - The St. Will Be on Team
Slide Marketing Profitability of Around One
Percent Puch System Which Has Quite Good Fruit
Potential in India and their expectations
Sector-28 20% off per night printing charges
Panasonic is the best company in this sector
and Craft Work Immediately Tips
It so happened that Kishanji could not go, friends.
Integrated Oil and Gas in this we
Oil will have to be stored separately and gas
have to look at it differently because
Oil dependency is gradually decreasing
and the dependence on gas is increasing.
If the gas business is going then it will definitely
Well, and so Reliance Industries in this
And India's landing company market cap
According to the change, Reliance
Industries is a big player in this but
If we are okay with such retail investors
So from Reliance, definitely from Mukesh Ambani.
They too will have to learn how to use their oil
The party that would reduce the weight of business on it
Reliance Jio service is being used in them
And your digital service from retail this jo
Amar Singh is the sector and there is a lot of focus on it.
If we have done this, then we should give such retail investors to them.
You have to copy it as you will see in this
Definitely the share price is very low so thirty
From seven percent to management of 6%
We really expect to see growth.
And the profit is the voting percentage.
But this Joe St. on 13
that it includes Reliance Retail and Digital
There is a huge portion of services, so
Oil dependency to gradually decrease
If it is, then definitely it is absolutely aggressive.
Should not be if Reliance Retail is
If you ever come to the outside list,
Our First Priority and Reliance Retail
Thank you, see you next
This sector is the advancement of practice.
It is also important because of the weight
that scenes per dont 63.51 which is the best
Company in this sector but effective
Expecting a two-day Kharak only
Profitability is all shot down to 189 percent
Against K Inspector Such Growing Sector
Which should be keeping in Ionic and they
Expect to worry about at least one person that
should speak at a good opportunity
During correction, thank you should be given to the person
The meeting is worthy
That this is thank you Jai Kishan ji, yes friends
Again the next sector is the fastest
The airline sector is a growing sector
But there is a lot of competition for Rising Oil.
Due to the rate, sales growth in this
There are many different profit groups.
Looks like a fast departure from airlines
Even after that, people like money then the full effect
The impact is on these lights
If the scientist had been perfect, he would have been 90% Schezwan
He came to the shift percent and his big
Impact is visible in profit because
Boiled fight a little bit those who airport
What cost the standing for students
etc. then your salary remains
If so, there will be a huge dip in profits.
Let us see what 1872 percent is.
Definitely should stay away from it for now as
Increase in profits and sales
If we come into positivity then we
Butt can be activated slowly
Definitely the sector is good for doctors
And we should pay attention to it
This is because transport services are advanced
10 Actors Obsess Fast YouTube to Wait
Porn Havya ITC on YouTube channel
Monopoly Company in these facts and figures
Definitely shipping and I want it soon
Spinner WhatsApp.com to six percent negative
Growth from 50% including negative profit margin
Monopoly Company Previous Want To Avoid Any
The company made Sector-20 Chutki an NIR
CTC coordinator friends who is also
Facility Facilities Economics Running
Hey friends, let me give you an example, 40
Companies like the year before made a splash
was but as if make their call
Firstly, people have a lot of money, so they
Definitely use the money for travelling.
Looking at India's growing economy
Companies like Wonderla have done very well
Infrastructure and High Quality Company
It is made but of long gown and economic
The entire impact of bad things is on Saturn.
It is visible that there is end drop from 98%
He almost completely lost his license.
Our sales are down by 95%.
This turnaround will be seen in the annual reports as well.
And now we have two hundred percent profit.
If you look at it, it will definitely be away from the present.
But it should remain an imaging sector company.
and as soon as the condom improves its
Also it will respond back and when it does
Definitely we should focus on respectable facilities.
should keep
Last day of G Next Sector Specialty
Paytm Now if you want to see Milan's movie then nowadays
Poor net has to see this very
If you can't, we will keep watching you until the right time.
Honey is completely banned in PVR too, nobody can
Usko First Kand Go To Cinema Crust Watch
Sushil Profitability IS from the Movie
Impacted but TCS opening of North
Inferior coming back to growth in directions
The company is Tubelight
It happened to you Kishanji friends, what we just said
All 500 companies in front of Sector-7
If you discuss it with him, you might think that
This is very complicated, some research is needed.
Chanel stickers could be straight for this
It is necessary or the research work remains completed
So Warren Buffett's partner is Charlie
But which is considered one of the best inventions
that fit inside the door
He sets himself higher expenses than
Charlie Murthy Style Ko To Chart Duniya
There is anything in it, if you keep it simple
If you keep it then definitely maximum number of people
If you can use it, then comment on our profit.
Also friends, this is our note, this thing is so
Let's keep it simple, someone is leading and someone else is
Are you an officer or a college going student?
is that white be able to do any research and
Research friends is not a big deal at all
The name of the research is not big, the process is big
It is very easy, so I request all of you.
I would like to say that our wealth creation
This program is online and free.
You must attend because you will
A process will be known in which process
We have found all the students in front of you.
If you have been able to present some things then all this
Things in a very simple format
An experienced teacher who is also an inverter himself
If our future is there then we not only
Do the stitching, butt guides too
So this is the most important thing we need to learn.
I definitely need it and Asha has learnt this thing from many people.
It remains in people's minds that I have twelve
Hours Shirdi will have to do very few things
I will keep lagging behind, will I be able to do it or not?
I will find it now and that's why I'll tell you
I am a doctor and so because of crying
There was a lot of work pressure last year.
But still why are we able to do research?
Because when a simple and easy method is told
That matter is there if you spend even half an hour every day
Even if you give it initially, you will still do it well.
You will find that getting troll results is important.
So you will definitely see this result.
All of you listen to this presentation carefully.
That you are very sad in this fort, thank you.
I speak and look towards profit from it
So I welcome you to sell
Create for your entire family and
for your retirement and whatever you
The financial goal bore the roots of the Federation in that
I welcome you all, thank you.
Amazing experience very good karma
The way you and Jai Kishan ji measured the height
Stocks lined up from their high guru
Found where the demand is already there, I think
You people should see the demand because this
The crying act that defeats me already
We did not apply till 7.30 and 8.
See, now if in a down bird of choice also
You find companies that are against
Tank battles to execute demands on your
Top in demand
Gautam approached the side one first.
The companies are listed and the location where the companies are located
The business is going great and below you
And companies too instead whose demand is limited
Gurgaon Branch Blackmail This Sir Weather
Priya look at the whole thing like PVR or Wonderla
Or are there any other companies that are not bad?
This will tell the history of all the companies.
The glass is not done. He takes the consistency.
Companies with road map but it affected
To whom because of family like and compassion
Just because of this, the business of the temple is fast.
So here is Jai Kishan ji in my opinion.
You don't have to worry about the downside if the same sector
If I look at other companies, I think
I am afraid this issue will happen.
I thought I would do it, but
Many companies have made sales profits.
How can this happen, I'm really
Amazing that in such a bad situation, he is able to make his profit
Then I'm going to have to come
Confidence goes away that when the good time will come
Since then these companies have done wonders, God bless you.
You company heaven we people valuation answer
I will give you and before that I will subscribe
Come to the thank you page.
Where I met I thanked everyone
Tha ok dogs down or down from thanks
I need the operation next Sunday, all this next
Sunday 90 A who belongs to Rajput
He and his team will be complete in their team
I went to India and drank honey and ghee like them.
I will put these students who are doing research
After finding them out, you will get the result as per your requirement.
Hey, what did you do and in front of you
Will do it next Sunday for 90 subscribers
in the results
Now come to the addition of the chilli peppers.
It is up to you people to get verification GN.
I will throw that query at this product.
I should lie down or
to Ajay
If yes, then I could find it and Kishan ji and everyone
Delivered to you guys by Good Morning
It has been said that at least this Sunday meeting
When I read these people's names, good
Morning Good Morning Good Morning
From India it happens that let us come to your
Till now we used to meet every year in the city, now in the city
I can't find it, but let's talk.
I get my confidence back after reading your name
It comes that Jal all is well and avoid going
On Right 5 Lines President and Karan Raj Yoga
or good morning
That and queries of issue Pradhan ji good
Morning
ok uncle Jitendra Singh Arya Jitendra ji
Yes, I am saying which is the best, see when
was presenting his screening test
To know about the Father is that Supreme and
Who is the best in me, so which one did I choose?
I have set an alarm, share it with someone else
Channel Discuss If There's Any Problem We'll Watch
So Supreme Industries is the best in the market.
It's great, everything is good and of good quality
It may also be found in this
in which do
Good but the other one has a lot of quality
If it is good then we will get punishment of value and group.
If I have to carry a combination then I
Personally, if investing in this chapter
I can invest in both if I want.
Sir O
that all Raj means those who after the extra
Oil is every member of the mix and tak group
Backward City College Five We're Great Company
That too has died, no matter how many crosses you have
Skin, don't think that you talked about the Supreme
Talking about getting superhit that we
When everyone invests the most in Supreme
Astral's IPO will not come in full
Otherwise we talked about the Supreme but you
After Ash Tomorrow is Marigold Committee any doubt
This surgical brother does not have high hopes
Have you got the answer to your question or
and available in the department cannot
Vikas Abhyankar I know Vikas Bank
No, I don't know which city the companies are from.
Like their soon angry mobile with us
companies also have a lot more because now
We
of the connection board that your bike should
Wait, how will we express our feelings and
Guess the time, early afternoon
So I would like to thank them for that.
He asked a great question, but this
Speaking of the best questions
I would like to say that these three companies which have been mentioned
That Guru is from the emerging sector and
There is tremendous demand in Amar Singh Sector
and because of high demand their PM is high
remains so if we look at the traditional way
So people get scared after seeing this appeal that
I will invest in it but
One should keep in mind that along with P, Arvind should also be there.
A lot of it is coming from below, if you
I bought something and its value was ₹10, so next year
Morning is also going to be rough and whatever you have
I bought it for ₹100 for the benefit of others, so it's yours
Pacific but rising from further down
If it is good for you then drink slowly and reduce it.
If it is going to happen then it will definitely happen in the company.
There should be aggression because three-four
After a year you will find Jaipur City in it.
Big feet
Please do, but I will speak at the convention.
We should definitely just do it
A Secret Fund Located at Great Opportunity
keep that we rather like in it but
Very few positives in a high quality company
See that he's not very much like this
It happens and there is a lot of demand too.
So I definitely want this entire focus to be on
If you have a long term vision, then do it with a little
Buying even at higher revolutions
There is no mistake
Yes, that is absolutely correct in your meeting and
Or would you like to like Jai Kishan ji?
Mixer Millennium is not spotted in sleep
And beneficial the growth rate list of root.
Its percentage backward plate use has been fixed
Is
I am reminded of Vijay here.
Like Krishna ji, we have been doing this for years.
Lal Path used to comment on the lips but Lal Path lips
If it is not moving for 3 years then time is also in our stomach.
I used to think that there was more love
Pimples should not appear in future
The developed countries will have arrested with
If he is in group A, then this gives you an idea.
Now, there is no need to stop it in the media.
Look, when anger comes, we will read it back.
I will feel in fact that I last week
Lal Path I have booked my first profit
And profit booking five percent profit
booked now doesn't mean I
The test result was positive when
If the rest of the people are negative then we are the regulators.
All this on the basis of how soft and smooth it is.
The companies went away from you people.
I will request you to take a good company whenever you want.
Let's start with taking half percent.
This depends on Mukesh's quantity.
Be freckled that your face might as well be
Why because when you are taking it to a rally
My Sher on Kumar Jain alias Tinu Diye
When Babbar and others came, I became more accurate.
Show live on strong to commit knew
that sugarcane is going to grow in the same way
start good companies that
to buy a small quantity and when the shares fall
There is revenue and brighter to not take tension
It has become clear that the future has its rights.
Vikas G and Let's Move Toward Next
I remember you, thank you, I removed PCS
Nishan Joshi at ward level to demand
English this can be accurate to demand
Anyone
I spoke to you on your demand, yes yes.
You won't find it anywhere, what does it do to your mind?
Okay, sir, you should keep two ways in mind.
If he is a salaried person then definitely he
A major correction should be announced.
No need to wait because it is of high quality
I will not give them any correction in thought and
Even if correction comes, it comes after two to three years.
If it comes then you will not invest till that time.
If you do this then it will definitely not be logical.
By doing this tip we should go into it I
Personal concern is regular monthly income
I will definitely do it for him that he just
Do it is in
I can still do that to you.
And its previous market definitely and second
So the companies that the team has, in addition to the brains
He asked what he was not ashamed of.
The team's business economist and
If this is an office related business then the address
There is absolutely no need for this to happen
Mute the level while sitting straight
You can do it in this but gradually means a lot
If the address is large, do not enter a large amount.
If you want to deposit your ₹100 then you put ₹10 bead.
Let's just say how British Khurram is.
You should keep it in your body, friend, give it a test
You can keep two to three percent because Amar
Leo is if you want to start performing
It will happen gradually but as its
Cent profit will increase our confidence too
If we increase, we will get five by going one level.
percent is location can now we on this
You give 2% on strength, statue leaders
You fry this and what is the condition means ever
Bigg Boss Birbhu
Duke time I felt like this this year
I will do it last but I did it well
He did this, this is my expectation
Make a profit and subscribe
Which alarms are included in the subscription?
Show what you have set
Singham Sub Chakulia Location Wise
Aram Photo Five Percent of Your Portfolio
Question is very comfortable soil and
I would like to say that earlier people used to say that this 10
What have you made in a year and you saw it
It would be that I keep bringing it consistently
My friends told me that I
in a while
That now such a good company where our brother
If happy then the meeting is held and will be held
I can give you my choice, will you let me sit with everyone now?
When will you take it, I also have to ask, when will it come?
It is not a mistake that he did not give you the role.
A good company to do is give some buy back
No, but all the goods will not last in life.
In Kaisa Lalpur also the question was raised that the country's
many soldiers
Yes, but very much, hey friend, you are my answer
Chuki Hai End Up
On the next bed I come Lalit Joshi
Lalit ji in Mumbai's workshop and these brothers
Perhaps you will also remember that it has been given in advance
Chrome Vapi Yes-Yes says Lalit Joshi
S gift sycamore in developed countries which are
In India also saint will come and what will
The incident will impact companies in
HDFC AMC Sir what is our tree
The recipe is written, but there is a language problem.
I was going to have to worry about going further
There is no ETF dear group will do but it
A better group than us will do penetration
It's not there now, but you can express your opinion.
And Defence Sir will definitely run from teacher
But the company which manages the ATM is better than the ATM.
It will continue because it is an emerging sector.
I have a video back so there is a lot of growth in it.
There is no lag and expenses as well
So
that the management of the company and Vijendra
It will remain because we take the gold and no one else
Take the product and get benefit from it.
It doesn't mean it works at all, but
Use this powder in agricultural land
I have not understood whether I should buy agricultural land.
So now I'm going to add the length value.
I will see that Hisar can get production out of it.
If it was then it was a production by yourself.
Dividends and other things will not come from here.
If things get good then the growth will happen.
It will definitely be good in this, how much tube
If he will not be able to reduce the large stock then
My press council will remain with the army staff
Do it this way, it is direct and also MP
I don't need to worry about Lavni
I don't know the whole period anymore.
I am but Navneet ji is doing it for Delhi
Years were added to ours in my hand when
Also, the Delhi meeting, that thing you tell me this
Not that you have no interest when it comes to time estimation
I am going to write down what you asked.
and you type sector idea in that
Gift for Investment Fund Investment
Limited, so you guys have completed this
Presentation Call on Fund Limited We
Which sector should I invest in first?
Also wrote this from the by video found below
Below is the other side which is the best part of the presentation.
I think Zardari is growing up.
And the people at the bottom were heroes and perhaps these
It should be done that the company which is at the bottom
People have a disease, baby, don't give me knowledge, keep doing it.
You are great and in demand, entry is there.
Now Jassar had played it well here.
Different who have limited front from their
So I would like to say that definitely at
We have kept the series Advertising Media
Apple root and mobile that Akshay if you ten
Snake meanwhile the company is top player caught then
If you see, the tension profit is tremendous.
If it is running then in which shares and profit
Both are consistency, that should be given priority
And the first 15 to 20 sectors 15 20
In the companies he
Jhal Gradually Thodi Bangles Mode Start
that their portfolio is definitely growing rapidly
Sir, it will increase, I did not tell you at all.
I would close myself in the same way.
I am the one whose reason I am broken, take care of it, oh what
Whose business is growing well
Friends, thanks for the correction, Jhalurai achievement
It would be good if G's credit is cleared.
Lovely ji has told brilliant stop
Election now both often now I top it
I would like to say, take them and let's all go
Problem staff selection was many before
Coming to profit because we now tip
But because of people, there are many and when we are really
How to do CK staff selection and
That's as easy as profit permits
If there is a method, then it seemed to us the best and this
The entire selection that we have done is Sir Kilometer
has done that and that's very easy you and
Anyone can do it, so do staff selection.
I am very thankful to you Sir for this
I wish that because of whom we could learn this
Jhaal definitely hey what is he saying that
From this contest, just like you were fully
Great full audio important knowledge too much to
Date of birth no thank you and ko today same
If you are sharing something with people
This vine is viral due to multiplication, however you
This will help many people in the future.
If you keep it, there is nothing like that
Me and Let Mirch a group where is Ravindra
Kumar Dhamija Night Vision Kishan Ji
That this friend, thank you all my entire team Jagdish
Patel Nice presentation Saria Jagdish Bhai
Honey Prashant Khare Wonderful from UP Gujarat
Presentation and Tamil injection G Prashant
Yes, you too will be ready in two-three hours.
We will show you the speed you want to see right now.
Changing Room Indoor Pramod Gangurde Very
Good presentation problem, come from village to Mumbai
And now we were in the workshop Yadav
For you in the Yes-Yes Advanced Workshop
Pramod Bhai, I hope I got it in advance.
Everything's Going for a Day
And Pankaj Rana Hot Pak Team Excellent or
Pankaj ji and next time Pankaj Rana ji sorry
A great presentation to watch
Thappad is a very nice presentation because
Tak Pay From Surat Mayank Sharma Wonderful
presentation or thank you table and on this
I think you are busy Mahendra Bhai.
So perhaps this did not happen in the state.
from India and that
Where can I loot, from the individual, from the whole
Control and Chip Indore-Amritsar
Presentation will not last
Impressions were made different different better
That is, you will be busy and will be first
Family job ghee and with it your
Ashok can stay under pressure by balancing
Neeraj Jain Thanks for holding a
I am Manoj's wife, almost control sector or
Manoj Bhai, the effort was that all
The system should be at least
A Very Good Weather Station Villain Smile and
Jacqueline told you guys that 15 Nitin Patel
Nitin Patel Surat he said you are very good
It's working because it took us time.
But it's a great workhorse and we're working with pins.
set then next next two
That when Delhi thanks Nitin Bhai Hemant
Kumar Agarwal or How are my heights?
I think Hemant Agarwal's name is also there.
Everyone who watches our live sessions
Hello, should I bring Aryan?
A View from Surat and Excellent
Ignoring ventilation in March and you
I wish you all the best of luck
Also Milind Bhai Jai Kishan ji is on the side of these people
had progressed very far
Vipin Chauhan, who has been robbed, good presentation or
Vipin G & I Hope Help Find Mumbai
I deal with OK, Good Education Regards
Shaving off money by preventing lots of
Money definitely and that mike he owns me
It took a decade to skin it all and my
And the money wasted in lakhs and in nine lakhs
I think I invested in you.
No, let's go today
Jitendra Singh feels that there is some obstacle in
And in the morning presentation thank you very much
Profit from Eating or Energy Watch Now
This is the work that I have done, otherwise I would have done this
Jaikishan and the entire team have not done it once
Please Sir ji
Where did the pyramid reach that my eye hum
And you'll take 5 more minutes of free time and do something important.
Frisbee is let me check-out
that his brother Jitendra has said that the stand
About sheet on my email ID ok so we work
We will do it, there is a video in the same.
Presentation meetings will keep the real truth and
It is possible that whatever presentation people made
He saw this presentation
that he has a complete action film
Can download Psoriasis Pucca OK
Jitendra ji, let's meet everyone.
Manoj Pandit will thank you all members period
Puri How Much Correction Effigy Correction Hona
Should be the first among the companies in the sector
So I think it's better than you making corrections.
That you are a Focus Quality Company
If correction is granted, an Additional Sessions Judge
It may not be possible, but it is not possible
If you get it then use it, then I
Because we don't have that
that I suddenly cut three to four percent of the potatoes
If you want to do stuffing then you can just make egg bhurji.
This is my personal view of going to the area.
Do 100 any point of time which food also
Gas Switch Milan can withdraw cash.
Withdrawal is always and absolutely agreed upon.
Do it because you did not get it but Atma Yash Patel
Sanjeev will dance in the hands of Economy
is in
How will I be in the future?
How does one grow without a Guru?
You can get an appointment like Ahmed Kumar
Agarwal very educative thanks thank you
To you too Saroj Das who is our Meghna
Jitendra Jain like this
And he has written please explain
Dashrath who is the best friend
Open Bluetooth settings for profit
that minba this kishan ji yes when bike level
I don't believe that we can tell in a minute.
How can I take Sharad Dhup?
I think our results will be
We are going to have every presentation in a hurry.
No need to do this whatsoever, complete this
If you hate from within, because our
He is going to discuss in great detail
What could this current be in quantity?
After the trek, we will do it in two-three days.
If you are going to have one then it is definitely necessary to wait.
It never happens in the market that you
Lutie gets on for minutes and
Nutritional changes occur when ghrelin and
Odisha Odisha means I think first I
I hope he grows up and you do too.
May you be well and help many people.
This time table will be taking final correction
Start like this and this is in my channel
Definitely subscribe to the company and look at a
Few Minutes Every School Tips
that those 20 minutes the second thing about it is
Under this company is technology back
Specific Profile All Doctors Lawyers In
India and washing machine for minutes
Credit Duty Love You to Buy Washing Machine
operator and
Ko Un Videsh Data Analytics Tuesday
Difficult to Beat Team Guys and Beneficial
Water in the last quarter meet points
From 65 customers this quarter, you get 10
Customer and loan growth explained
23next customers have simply gone that fiber
Glue Simply This Means a Definite Product
Launch to 10 customers and a product of
Eggs in this company and nine major passes
Growing Companies in India This Will Act
Passed Agromet 50% Tiger End
Expecting a Small Utna Withrow Saffron
2530 percent you can speak on your profile
I took that electrolyte as told
Continue the recipe every month if you get the chance.
Keep collecting, says Neeraj Jain
Please suggest if you all for Bandhan peg
The matter was discussed in London and Paris.
That sir I had lost all my bikes
Instead of level, I gave them a little space to sit.
I would say that because a lot of
Moratorium on the issue and question are
If he is against it then he is far away from that chapter.
As soon as the results come, we will do more on that.
You will be able to tell them in the edifice, but if such
If there is no need for it at the moment, then vision
Prakash Reddy is bad and where is the first Jain placed?
Milling Bhai Bandhan Bank HDFC Bank Where
So both broke Redmi 2 ₹2 so the first joint
Keep the money in your pocket as per your requirement.
There is no question, well there are as many sides as there are
Milan Bhai told that there is more traffic here.
The inspector broke the first set of bonds.
We will take you to Vikas Bhawan, thanks for telling
Friend brother, you also know what Vikas says.
collection and very good question says that
Tag a stop rally in that correction
I am in this because you say you are in correction
So add but how to a normal interest
You will know that this too is in correction mood.
Milling is all about looking at it fundamentally.
You can also look at the technical aspects, so this
The normal investor is that technical chart
They understand more quickly
Data is used for fundamental investing.
There is definitely a lot and after watching the chat
Can you tell me what rally means to become a hero?
go away if that's the stock price then its
Delhi border will say and if there is correction
So if you keep saying take and hello then that update
technical part were fundamental if we
If you see, then Potli research continuously
If it is increasing then it is in rally mode and the price is also
Supports rally mode, the time end
If don't have it like but after if we
Will see the last time companies distance
Factor in Change Profit Brought Down
So he is in correction mood
You can tell me the problem
There was also an FD here which is written like
The entire spreadsheet that is in front of you, when
Ashok Bhai, keep whatever is there, it will work on this only.
You are saying cut, come on open the com till then
So that sometimes we can explain and do it
But as mentioned in the chart,
HDFC is the largest housing finance company
He is selling vegetables and there is no profit in it.
Add these correction modes to the crispy
Profits will increase later all over the world
She will run like I absolutely told her all this
that he played between his name and the LTTE
Mr Nishant Jyoti Thank you, I will enjoy
The duration of the question paper or tissue is complete.
Memories from Delhi, that will soon be mine
My memory is sharp, I remember their names now.
I also have companies with my name on them.
Unique about which meeting you're in
that this is an interesting topic okay and
According to the criminal, the global judge
Particular topic is delete buying level above
The road is a good question right now, can you tell me?
How do we judge when the time has come to take
I only work in profit and sales when
Consolidation breaks down, meaning years and years.
If a stock moves in a country, its
Profits for example sales of 20 crores
Continuity is going on and if there is a lot of growth in sales
250 crore end profit gets bored
And from 100 crores it becomes 100 crores and a quarter.
So we can also call it technical record.
are and a range if from the side of profit
If it breaks then Bangalore will definitely be formed.
is in it
torch light or something saying that you
The leaf felt like Singh's Just to 8 light
If we want to try it like a submarine, then
If you haven't subscribed, be sure to
The cost effective Nirali Mode effective se
pregnant dhup rekha notification
Identify the best of the training delivery
Fans find it difficult to identify during
Bay Contested and Gives Pain Area Where
you got your daughter
And madam was doing a very simple calculation
Like I am also earning this right now.
Kishanji is getting killed, is this any retired person?
Otherwise, you know what all these people will do.
I am not doing you any wrong, Kishan ji.
Brother, predict that you people probably now
Get ready to ask every month
Friends, if you must be biking a little bit
Someone is a Vihar running member and who is retired
have to take them in proper form when
The market falls and what does it mean?
There were 15 others on the other side and he got a call from the other side.
How much they say, Kamal saw that now he
After taking all the companies on time
I meet the Lord but when I talk back
Since I am living here, I sell a little bit of goods every month.
I keep collecting it but every time I
I also ensure that Ayurveda
I will never say through him that he has fallen a lot and taken everything
Take this five star for ever more decline
I must always be B's Shri
Thank you Pooja ji to you Sanjay Agarwal ji
say knees
Question, thank you, Sanjay ji, town you are
The most prominent on Chief Minister like
Me Hug Lasts For Youtube Videos
and help others in taking in form division
Heart Center and Selection Selection your if it
Felt that there was a motivation for us too
These are the things that the development bank should be given by the opposition party
Diwali portfolio from stocks
Deepak back selects what I
Diwali stocks were given to innocent people
I want it as Diwali gift, you know?
See all this on Diwali and before Diwali
If I too had all this every Diwali in our
If we change the stock then we will not get gas.
Companies should stay where they can
There are 12 companies in the front and back, like that side
The issue of Nazara has just come out, it is Guru Industries
But there is a little problem with the quality.
We have not put in this good quality
We will see how deep it is by the coming Diwali.
are doing till
If it works out, we'll add them too.
But don't think like this, Diwali Diwali Diwali
We have talked about the words rally and correction.
Use Share That Correction Halfway Through
So whenever you get a chance, the signal comes to your place.
First time in fundamental knowledge in you
people go on the tube every day throughout the week
Everyone do research together if you have this
felt that hard work
That this Sanket ji is your Mehuwala neck
exhibitions thank you I also you and
Keep in mind that this is
I am my Alka Abhinav Bhai ok Vikas Bhai
Whole world to learn how to use laptop and
The Fundamental Analysis for the Best Gift
Fundamental Date of Birth Complete What to Do
What have Jaikishan and Meeting Bhai done?
Looted Lucky Collected and Current Trend
and together within a few days
What does management think about the people who are
These three things are being worked on during the day.
Combined, we get the perfect squeeze
Harpal Singh Sir please suggest Mind Tree
And new cylinders are on one side of the people
Which of the two had just provided that
CBI team
Yes plane ji, we will see more or Jai Kishan Jai Kishan
Yes, you say Om is one.
It happened with Jackie Chan ji, he says Harpal
Singh's Mindtree
what video will you give mind your
Exam company but I think it is quality
The company also launched this bell inductor control.
Actress Acting Tips Looking Into
WhatsApp setting on NPR and all
Chhoti si to mai chalegi holiday company
Why will we run because it is on the IT sector
Why because it wants that 10 years 12
Subscribe for 15 years without any problem.
Can its history be cleared first?
Published 29 Nov 10 2013
that if I have then management will improve
You don't need to sell it, it's a matter of version
If those are not priorities then Sanjay will go.
Told that this was his first place but he had adopted it.
Is
And Naveen Shyoran feels Ajmer
Chemical Permeation Too much chemical you have
After the special Rafi blast from the problem of
I accompanied the direction of and new fluoride and back
If it comes after then I will definitely watch the match.
that the company which is the highest quality
If there is consistency then we can change our diet
Definitely see reference Naveen Sheoran
It is a great company, no doubt about it
And the entire sector is running, so
Second and third-ranked companies also
It will run and try making a good profit but
We if high quality consistency and long
If you look at the term wealth creation, on the back
I would like to go to
Hey friend, thank you Mili brother, thank you very much
And Nishant Kshatriya will be absolutely right on your side
Highly Appreciated Shift by Profit In
Thank you Nishant ji, yours too Sanket Jain
I AM FOREST IN YOUR CHANNEL AND LIVE
Session what is the indication of the bike, this is today
If we are online then look at the line first.
We will keep meeting Guru but you people have one thing
The tag noted that he had been living in Dubai for ten years.
I humm's right in front of us
Morning ma'am, no holiday, meeting is on
I have done it exactly, let us update it.
Always if you guys are 15 minutes early in the session
If you come, you will always find some leaders or
It is not my habit to attend any meeting.
If I go 15 minutes earlier, I will meet some leaders.
There will be a conversation even if you come 15 minutes late.
People will leave and I will be able to talk to the leader.
So this is my old habit of ours.
Bigi Vrat Try Time or Double Six
A nice presentation friend thank you 200
Jitendra Singh's son Shabbir was in charge
Very nice presentation, thanks Sudhir
Brother, I hope so today
Presentation leads us to wealth creation
This and upcoming shoe presentation will be given
There are six eggs, these six Sundays, you can have as many as you want.
You talked about the company, all this is about the company.
What will you do now after the results?
If he goes, he will be here all the coming Sundays.
0.5 inch profit from morning 950
8am Thank you, welcome everyone
Ka Milan Price, thank you very much Jai
Kishan ji, thank you very much for your data.
Nowadays I don't have time, Jai Kishan, please give me 2 hours.
We all said father or this was a picture
How much time did you spend making the picture?
Now butter the whole team is with us ok us
It never felt like we were alone
I know equal officers
Milind likes that it's easy to collect data.
No, no, but we have a data master.
Like Ashok Bhai, he also has this Vijay Bhai.
Yes Prashant ji, the entire details are slow.
This presentation is not complete for both of us.
Profit from its team's hai toh yaar*
President Uddhav, this was just the trailer
The entire movie is still left, so here are the reactions.
Vijay Kishan ji plays the role of brightness
You and your team will get the result
She will admit but these people did everything for the result
Ninth's management stations will be more
Subscribe to Dhundh Matlab our regular
When there is a conversation, they are given tremendous
If you have done this presentation then please give ₹10 Anil
Reports of high-ranking figures meeting diplomats
It seems your presentation is an hour long.
This is it but friends, in making this picture
Couldn't do it in the shortest time
interest and I would tell you guys that two
that you look look look perfect now all these
Thank you very much for taking care of your health
Keep that proper track as it continues to grow
Jai Hind Sir